The menu is so important.
菜单很重要.
Yes, we're working on it.
Yes, 我们正在致力于它.
We're interviewing for a new chef.
我们正在面试一名新主厨.
Good. Our head chef makes the restaurant very exciting.
Good. 我们的主厨使餐厅非常令人兴奋.
Jarmusch Blok.
Jarmusch Blok?
Jarmusch Blok. Where is he from?
Jarmusch Blok. 他来自哪里?
Poland. Actually,
波兰. 事实上,
it's an interesting story. He first came to the U. S.
这是个很有趣的故事. 他最初来到美国
with a Polish...
是跟一个波兰的...
-Circus.   -Yes.
-马戏团. -Yes.
Jarmusch the Clown.
小丑Jarmusch.
He was a famous juggler.
他是个著名的杂耍人.
-No       -Yes.
-不是吧   -是的.
-He used kitchen knives.
-他使用菜刀.
-Really?  -Whatever happened to him?
-Really?  -他后来发生了什么?
He left the circus and went solo.
他离开马戏团单干.
Ah. Is there much work for knife-jugglers in the United States?
Ah. 在美国 有很多工作给玩刀子的吗?
Well, he worked in a comedy club in New York.
Well, 他在一个喜剧俱乐部工作 在纽约.
He had a routine based on food.
他有一个固定节目 基于食品.
That's where our C. E. O. Jim Bigelow found him.
那是我们执行总裁Jim Bigelow 发现他的地方.
Jim Bigelow?
-Mr. Bigelow.  -Mr. Bigelow?
-Mr.Bigelow.  -Mr.Bigelow?
He found out Jarmusch
他发现Jarmusch
had worked at the Hotel Europa in Warsaw,
曾在华沙的Europa酒店工作
as a fully-trained chef.
作为一名训练有素的主厨.
But after six months Jarmusch left for the circus.
但6个月后Jarmusch 离开了 去了马戏团.
So Jarmusch the Clown is now Jarmusch the Chef.
So 小丑Jarmusch 现在成了主厨Jarmusch.
But does he still juggle kitchen knives?
但他仍然玩厨房的菜刀吗?
Not when I'm around!
我在时他不玩.